https://www.bamboobat.com/privacy-policy/

Your Privacy
At BamBooBat Store we always try to protect your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
What information do we collect? How do we use it?When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.When you submit a customer review, we also ask for your e-mail address, although you can choose not to have your e-mail address displayed with your review.When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.We personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about electronics and other merchandise that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the store.We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, just send an email to info@bamboobat.com telling us.How does BamBooBat Store protect customer information?When you place orders we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. None of your personal information or credit card data is kept on our servers.What about "cookies"?"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them.Will BamBooBat Store disclose the information it collects to outside parties?BamBooBat Store does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. BamBooBat Store may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.Children's GuidelinesWe care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to: Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. In summaryWe are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at Loadedbases possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. If you never want to receive any announcements or special offers from us, send an email to info@bamboobat.com and let us know.Your consentBy using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by BamBooBat Store. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it
×
Join Our Mailing List for special offers!
Connect with Us:
©
bamboobat.com
Sitemap
Premium BigCommerce Theme by Lone Star Templates
